[{"problem_set":"Relative motion","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 08","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT15S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-05T04:31:33.000Z","end":"2017-05-05T04:31:48.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Relative motion","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 07","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT414S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-05T04:21:16.000Z","end":"2017-05-05T04:28:10.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Relative motion","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 05","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT423S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-05T04:04:00.000Z","end":"2017-05-05T04:11:03.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Relative motion","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT3S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-05T04:03:55.000Z","end":"2017-05-05T04:03:58.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Relative motion","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 09","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT11S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-05T04:03:42.000Z","end":"2017-05-05T04:03:53.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Chapter 1","problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 3","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT30S","actor":1,"start":"2017-05-05T03:58:00.000Z","end":"2017-05-05T03:58:30.000Z","class":"MCDB 310"},{"problem_set":"Relative motion","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 01","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT150S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-05T03:16:05.000Z","end":"2017-05-05T03:18:35.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Relative motion","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 01","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT159S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-05T03:13:22.000Z","end":"2017-05-05T03:16:01.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Relative motion","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 04","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT108S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-05T03:10:39.000Z","end":"2017-05-05T03:12:27.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Relative motion","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT3S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-05T03:10:28.000Z","end":"2017-05-05T03:10:31.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Relative motion","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT76S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-05T03:06:29.000Z","end":"2017-05-05T03:07:45.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Relative motion","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 09","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT377S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-05T02:59:31.000Z","end":"2017-05-05T03:05:48.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 02","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT9S","actor":2,"start":"2017-05-04T07:25:44.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T07:25:53.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 25","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT106S","actor":2,"start":"2017-05-04T07:23:47.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T07:25:33.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 09 Problem 02","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT41S","actor":2,"start":"2017-05-04T07:23:02.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T07:23:43.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 04","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT40S","actor":2,"start":"2017-05-04T07:22:05.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T07:22:45.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 10 Problem 08","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT32S","actor":2,"start":"2017-05-04T07:20:42.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T07:21:14.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 10 Problem 01","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT55S","actor":2,"start":"2017-05-04T07:19:41.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T07:20:36.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 07","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT54S","actor":2,"start":"2017-05-04T07:18:39.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T07:19:33.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 07 Problem 19","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT8S","actor":2,"start":"2017-05-04T07:18:01.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T07:18:09.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2014 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 15","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT43S","actor":2,"start":"2017-05-04T07:17:10.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T07:17:53.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 05","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT7S","actor":2,"start":"2017-05-04T07:16:58.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T07:17:05.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 07 Problem 19","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT22S","actor":2,"start":"2017-05-04T07:16:31.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T07:16:53.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 09 Problem 02","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT54S","actor":2,"start":"2017-05-04T07:15:33.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T07:16:27.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 05","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT62S","actor":2,"start":"2017-05-04T07:14:25.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T07:15:27.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 01","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT12S","actor":2,"start":"2017-05-04T07:14:07.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T07:14:19.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 07 Problem 12","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT46S","actor":2,"start":"2017-05-04T07:13:15.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T07:14:01.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 12","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT26S","actor":2,"start":"2017-05-04T07:12:45.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T07:13:11.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 11","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT52S","actor":2,"start":"2017-05-04T07:11:42.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T07:12:34.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 05","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT93S","actor":2,"start":"2017-05-04T07:10:04.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T07:11:37.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 07 Problem 19","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT74S","actor":2,"start":"2017-05-04T07:08:45.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T07:09:59.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 01","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT60S","actor":2,"start":"2017-05-04T07:07:30.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T07:08:30.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 08","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT29S","actor":2,"start":"2017-05-04T07:06:38.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T07:07:07.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 13","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT87S","actor":2,"start":"2017-05-04T07:04:26.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T07:05:53.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2013 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 07","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT50S","actor":2,"start":"2017-05-04T07:03:31.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T07:04:21.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 10 Problem 19","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT102S","actor":2,"start":"2017-05-04T07:01:36.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T07:03:18.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Newtonâ€™s Laws","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 13 Problem 09","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT66S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-04T02:58:42.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T02:59:48.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Relative motion","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 01","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT7S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-04T02:58:20.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T02:58:27.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Relative motion","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 05","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT18S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-04T02:58:00.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T02:58:18.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Relative motion","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 17","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT47S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-04T02:55:47.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T02:56:34.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Relative motion","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 04","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT8S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-04T02:55:38.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T02:55:46.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Relative motion","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 01","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT5S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-04T02:55:31.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T02:55:36.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Relative motion","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 07","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT8S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-04T02:55:21.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T02:55:29.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Relative motion","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 08","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT7S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-04T02:55:11.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T02:55:18.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"1D kinematics","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 10","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT333S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-04T02:45:10.000Z","end":"2017-05-04T02:50:43.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 07","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT14S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T23:53:27.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T23:53:41.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 11 Problem 02","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT15S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T23:50:53.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T23:51:08.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 09","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT321S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T23:18:55.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T23:24:16.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 16","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT320S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T23:13:10.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T23:18:30.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 16","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT58S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T23:11:42.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T23:12:40.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 07","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT254S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T23:06:17.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T23:10:31.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 03","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT5S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T23:02:30.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T23:02:35.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 13","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT28S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T23:01:47.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T23:02:15.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 01","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT5S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T21:09:47.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T21:09:52.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 01","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT296S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T21:02:34.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T21:07:30.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 01","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT20S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T21:01:56.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T21:02:16.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 12 Problem 09","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT26S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T21:00:10.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T21:00:36.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 11 Problem 02","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT31S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T20:58:13.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T20:58:44.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 14","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT45S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T20:57:22.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T20:58:07.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 07","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT66S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T20:56:03.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T20:57:09.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 07","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT28S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T20:55:31.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T20:55:59.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 12 Problem 10","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT4S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T20:55:10.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T20:55:14.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 12 Problem 10","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT35S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T20:53:45.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T20:54:20.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 08","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT193S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T20:47:07.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T20:50:20.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 09","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT41S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T20:46:22.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T20:47:03.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 07","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT198S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T20:39:28.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T20:42:46.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 01","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT212S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T20:35:18.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T20:38:50.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 12 Problem 06","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT183S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T20:31:33.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T20:34:36.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 09","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT73S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T20:29:05.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T20:30:18.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 13 Problem 09","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT26S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T20:28:17.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T20:28:43.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 10 Problem 02","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT4S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T20:27:58.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T20:28:02.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 10 Problem 02","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT29S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T20:27:10.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T20:27:39.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 04","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT8S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T20:27:01.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T20:27:09.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 04","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT255S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T20:22:03.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T20:26:18.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 03","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT284S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T20:14:39.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T20:19:23.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 03","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT197S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T20:08:38.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T20:11:55.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 08","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT123S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T20:06:14.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T20:08:17.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 04","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT20S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T20:05:35.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T20:05:55.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 11 Problem 02","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT38S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T20:04:27.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T20:05:05.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 11 Problem 05","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT58S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T20:02:47.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T20:03:45.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Exam Fall 11 Problem 01","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT27S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T20:01:49.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T20:02:16.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 06","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT408S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T19:30:24.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T19:37:12.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 11 Problem 10","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT14S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T19:29:30.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T19:29:44.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 03","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT30S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T19:08:54.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T19:09:24.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 09","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT105S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T18:57:43.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T18:59:28.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 18","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT124S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T18:55:16.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T18:57:20.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Scaling","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 4 Spring 11 Problem 05","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT115S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T18:48:26.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T18:50:21.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Scaling","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 02","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT15S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T18:47:50.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T18:48:05.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Scaling","problem":"Um Physics 135 Midterm 3 Fall 12 Problem 06","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT141S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T18:39:24.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T18:41:45.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Scaling","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 02","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT547S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T18:26:02.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T18:35:09.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Scaling","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 01","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT364S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T18:16:57.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T18:23:01.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Scaling","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 04","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT22S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T18:16:33.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T18:16:55.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Scaling","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 02","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT29S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T18:14:19.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T18:14:48.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Scaling","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 15","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT573S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T18:01:33.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T18:11:06.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Scaling","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 14","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT368S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T17:47:07.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T17:53:15.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Scaling","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 3 Winter 13 Problem 09","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT333S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T17:11:43.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T17:17:16.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 09 Problem 01","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT3S","actor":3,"start":"2017-05-03T16:34:11.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T16:34:14.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Mechanical waves","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 12","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT3S","actor":3,"start":"2017-05-03T16:33:52.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T16:33:55.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"1D kinematics","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 14","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT3S","actor":3,"start":"2017-05-03T16:33:34.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T16:33:37.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"1D kinematics","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 09","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT3S","actor":3,"start":"2017-05-03T16:33:25.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T16:33:28.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Vector algebra","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 05 Problem 19","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT12S","actor":3,"start":"2017-05-03T16:32:57.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T16:33:09.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Gases","problem":"PB5_038","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT53S","actor":4,"start":"2017-05-03T13:35:25.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T13:36:18.000Z","class":"Chemistry 130"},{"problem_set":"Scaling","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 1 Spring 11 Problem 02","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT124S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T04:32:32.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T04:34:36.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Scaling","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Fall 12 Problem 01","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT221S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T04:27:41.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T04:31:22.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Scaling","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 11 Problem 23","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT470S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T04:18:51.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T04:26:41.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Electric fields","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 05","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT1272S","actor":5,"start":"2017-05-03T04:02:37.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T04:23:49.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Scaling","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 13","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT203S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T04:14:49.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T04:18:12.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Scaling","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Fall 12 Problem 11","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT281S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T04:09:32.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T04:14:13.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Scaling","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Fall 12 Problem 02","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT151S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T04:00:02.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T04:02:33.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Scaling","problem":"UM Physics 135 Final Winter 12 Problem 24","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT70S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T03:57:50.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T03:59:00.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 04","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT24S","actor":5,"start":"2017-05-03T03:58:08.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T03:58:32.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 10","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT27S","actor":5,"start":"2017-05-03T03:57:28.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T03:57:55.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Scaling","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 12","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT46S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T03:56:12.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T03:56:58.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 10 Problem 01","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT209S","actor":5,"start":"2017-05-03T03:53:23.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T03:56:52.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Scaling","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 02","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT283S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T03:48:46.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T03:53:29.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 08","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT643S","actor":5,"start":"2017-05-03T03:42:12.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T03:52:55.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Scaling","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 13 Problem 04","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT570S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T03:33:35.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T03:43:05.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Scaling","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 12","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT465S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-03T03:18:40.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T03:26:25.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 16","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT96S","actor":6,"start":"2017-05-03T00:24:09.000Z","end":"2017-05-03T00:25:45.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 04","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT19S","actor":7,"start":"2017-05-02T23:38:44.000Z","end":"2017-05-02T23:39:03.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 07 Problem 19","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT121S","actor":7,"start":"2017-05-02T23:36:06.000Z","end":"2017-05-02T23:38:07.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2014 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 15","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT304S","actor":7,"start":"2017-05-02T23:30:48.000Z","end":"2017-05-02T23:35:52.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 07 Problem 12","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT32S","actor":7,"start":"2017-05-02T23:30:06.000Z","end":"2017-05-02T23:30:38.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 10","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT129S","actor":7,"start":"2017-05-02T23:27:46.000Z","end":"2017-05-02T23:29:55.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Coulomb's law","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 10 Problem 01","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT620S","actor":7,"start":"2017-05-02T23:15:12.000Z","end":"2017-05-02T23:25:32.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Chapter 1","problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 1","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT10S","actor":1,"start":"2017-05-02T18:03:48.000Z","end":"2017-05-02T18:03:58.000Z","class":"MCDB 310"},{"problem_set":"Chapter 1","problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 8","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT9S","actor":1,"start":"2017-05-02T18:03:38.000Z","end":"2017-05-02T18:03:47.000Z","class":"MCDB 310"},{"problem_set":"Chapter 1","problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 5","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT62S","actor":1,"start":"2017-05-02T18:02:08.000Z","end":"2017-05-02T18:03:10.000Z","class":"MCDB 310"},{"problem_set":"Chapter 1","problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 7","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT15S","actor":1,"start":"2017-05-02T18:01:49.000Z","end":"2017-05-02T18:02:04.000Z","class":"MCDB 310"},{"problem_set":"Measurements and Calculations","problem":"PB1_088","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT767S","actor":8,"start":"2017-05-02T17:36:57.000Z","end":"2017-05-02T17:49:44.000Z","class":"Chemistry 130"},{"problem_set":"Measurements and Calculations","problem":"PB1_040","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT7S","actor":8,"start":"2017-05-02T17:36:11.000Z","end":"2017-05-02T17:36:18.000Z","class":"Chemistry 130"},{"problem_set":"Chapter 1","problem":"MCDB310 Chapter 1 Problem 2","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT6S","actor":9,"start":"2017-05-02T03:54:41.000Z","end":"2017-05-02T03:54:47.000Z","class":"MCDB 310"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 1 Winter 12 Problem 01","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT3418S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-02T02:44:19.000Z","end":"2017-05-02T03:41:17.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Quiz 3 Spring 11 Problem 07","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT107S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-02T02:41:52.000Z","end":"2017-05-02T02:43:39.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Vectors","problem":"UM Physics 135 Midterm 2 Winter 11 Problem 10","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT40S","actor":0,"start":"2017-05-02T01:59:16.000Z","end":"2017-05-02T01:59:56.000Z","class":"Physics 135"},{"problem_set":"Final","problem":"PEF_10","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT34S","actor":10,"start":"2017-04-27T22:15:53.000Z","end":"2017-04-27T22:16:27.000Z","class":"Chemistry 130"},{"problem_set":"Exam 1","problem":"F11_E2_Q03","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT10S","actor":10,"start":"2017-04-27T22:15:30.000Z","end":"2017-04-27T22:15:40.000Z","class":"Chemistry 130"},{"problem_set":"Acids and Bases","problem":"PB15_032","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT20S","actor":11,"start":"2017-04-23T21:23:28.000Z","end":"2017-04-23T21:23:48.000Z","class":"Chemistry 130"},{"problem_set":"Chemical Equilibrium","problem":"PB14_002","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT2S","actor":11,"start":"2017-04-23T21:23:14.000Z","end":"2017-04-23T21:23:16.000Z","class":"Chemistry 130"},{"problem_set":"Chemical Equilibrium","problem":"PB14_002","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT5S","actor":11,"start":"2017-04-23T21:23:08.000Z","end":"2017-04-23T21:23:13.000Z","class":"Chemistry 130"},{"problem_set":"Acids and Bases","problem":"PB15_019","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT2S","actor":11,"start":"2017-04-23T21:22:56.000Z","end":"2017-04-23T21:22:58.000Z","class":"Chemistry 130"},{"problem_set":"Acids and Bases","problem":"PB15_019","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT1S","actor":11,"start":"2017-04-23T21:22:53.000Z","end":"2017-04-23T21:22:54.000Z","class":"Chemistry 130"},{"problem_set":"Acids and Bases","problem":"PB15_019","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT2S","actor":11,"start":"2017-04-23T21:22:48.000Z","end":"2017-04-23T21:22:50.000Z","class":"Chemistry 130"},{"problem_set":"Acids and Bases","problem":"PB15_029","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT4S","actor":11,"start":"2017-04-23T21:22:39.000Z","end":"2017-04-23T21:22:43.000Z","class":"Chemistry 130"},{"problem_set":"Chemical Equilibrium","problem":"PB14_046","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT4S","actor":11,"start":"2017-04-23T21:22:30.000Z","end":"2017-04-23T21:22:34.000Z","class":"Chemistry 130"},{"problem_set":"Final","problem":"PEF_12","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT2S","actor":11,"start":"2017-04-23T21:22:02.000Z","end":"2017-04-23T21:22:04.000Z","class":"Chemistry 130"},{"problem_set":"Final","problem":"PEF_12","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT11S","actor":11,"start":"2017-04-23T21:21:47.000Z","end":"2017-04-23T21:21:58.000Z","class":"Chemistry 130"},{"problem_set":"Bonding","problem":"PB9_015","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT20S","actor":12,"start":"2017-04-23T18:31:56.000Z","end":"2017-04-23T18:32:16.000Z","class":"Chemistry 130"},{"problem_set":"Bonding","problem":"PB9_053","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT11S","actor":12,"start":"2017-04-23T18:31:26.000Z","end":"2017-04-23T18:31:37.000Z","class":"Chemistry 130"},{"problem_set":"Circular motion","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 98 Problem 04","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT71S","actor":13,"start":"2017-04-22T14:55:04.000Z","end":"2017-04-22T14:56:15.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Circular motion","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 02 Problem 12","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT7S","actor":13,"start":"2017-04-22T14:38:47.000Z","end":"2017-04-22T14:38:54.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Circular motion","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 02 Problem 12","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT15S","actor":13,"start":"2017-04-22T14:38:06.000Z","end":"2017-04-22T14:38:21.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 13","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT171S","actor":14,"start":"2017-04-21T23:14:09.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T23:17:00.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Polarization","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 20","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT24S","actor":15,"start":"2017-04-21T23:14:16.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T23:14:40.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 10 Problem 22","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT128S","actor":15,"start":"2017-04-21T23:11:45.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T23:13:53.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 FA2010 Problem 16","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT6S","actor":16,"start":"2017-04-21T23:13:39.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T23:13:45.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 10 Problem 23","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT57S","actor":15,"start":"2017-04-21T23:10:27.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T23:11:24.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Polarization","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 14","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT8S","actor":15,"start":"2017-04-21T23:10:17.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T23:10:25.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Polarization","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 14","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT84S","actor":15,"start":"2017-04-21T23:07:39.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T23:09:03.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 15","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT268S","actor":17,"start":"2017-04-21T23:04:27.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T23:08:55.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Polarization","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 09","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT49S","actor":15,"start":"2017-04-21T23:06:17.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T23:07:06.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam WN2010 Problem 7","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT58S","actor":18,"start":"2017-04-21T23:04:35.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T23:05:33.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 14","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT241S","actor":18,"start":"2017-04-21T23:00:32.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T23:04:33.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Moment of inertia","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 02 Problem 08","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT47S","actor":17,"start":"2017-04-21T23:03:38.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T23:04:25.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Torque and rotational dynamics","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 01","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT33S","actor":17,"start":"2017-04-21T23:02:35.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T23:03:08.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Polarization","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 24","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT104S","actor":14,"start":"2017-04-21T23:00:44.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T23:02:28.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Static equilibrium","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 98 Problem 19","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT9S","actor":17,"start":"2017-04-21T23:01:31.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T23:01:40.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Torque and rotational dynamics","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 03","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT319S","actor":17,"start":"2017-04-21T22:55:19.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T23:00:38.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Radiation energy and momentum","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 22","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT105S","actor":14,"start":"2017-04-21T22:55:04.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:56:49.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Newton's laws","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 18","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT238S","actor":17,"start":"2017-04-21T22:51:19.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:55:17.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Polarization","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 09","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT269S","actor":14,"start":"2017-04-21T22:50:29.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:54:58.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 05","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT211S","actor":19,"start":"2017-04-21T22:50:00.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:53:31.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 3","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT130S","actor":17,"start":"2017-04-21T22:49:07.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:51:17.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Mechanical waves","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 6","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT244S","actor":19,"start":"2017-04-21T22:45:53.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:49:57.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Mechanical waves","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam WN2010 Problem 13","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT119S","actor":17,"start":"2017-04-21T22:46:38.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:48:37.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Sound","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam WN2010 Problem 6","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT14S","actor":20,"start":"2017-04-21T22:47:25.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:47:39.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Linear momentum","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 09 Problem 18","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT33S","actor":21,"start":"2017-04-21T22:46:53.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:47:26.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Gravitational force / potential energy","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 19","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT12S","actor":20,"start":"2017-04-21T22:47:07.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:47:19.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Mechanical waves","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 21","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT25S","actor":21,"start":"2017-04-21T22:46:07.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:46:32.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"1D kinematics","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 03","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT26S","actor":21,"start":"2017-04-21T22:45:35.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:46:01.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Gravitational force / potential energy","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Winter 04 Problem 14","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT193S","actor":22,"start":"2017-04-21T22:42:08.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:45:21.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Linear momentum","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 05 Problem 02","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT16S","actor":23,"start":"2017-04-21T22:43:39.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:43:55.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 24","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT29S","actor":23,"start":"2017-04-21T22:43:08.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:43:37.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Electromagnetic waves","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 21","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT11S","actor":24,"start":"2017-04-21T22:43:25.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:43:36.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Polarization","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Final Exam Problem 23","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT94S","actor":24,"start":"2017-04-21T22:41:37.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:43:11.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Gravitational force / potential energy","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 16","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT23S","actor":23,"start":"2017-04-21T22:42:28.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:42:51.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 10","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT6S","actor":23,"start":"2017-04-21T22:42:19.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:42:25.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Rolling motion","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Winter 04 Problem 09","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT19S","actor":23,"start":"2017-04-21T22:41:58.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:42:17.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Periodic motion","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 10","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT297S","actor":22,"start":"2017-04-21T22:37:02.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:41:59.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Mechanical waves","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 FA2010 Problem 20","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT30S","actor":23,"start":"2017-04-21T22:41:26.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:41:56.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 21","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT77S","actor":24,"start":"2017-04-21T22:40:09.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:41:26.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Vector algebra","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 98 Problem 14","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT61S","actor":10,"start":"2017-04-21T22:40:20.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:41:21.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Mechanical energy","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Winter 04 Problem 15","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT12S","actor":10,"start":"2017-04-21T22:39:40.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:39:52.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2013 Final Exam Problem 21","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT139S","actor":24,"start":"2017-04-21T22:37:28.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:39:47.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Linear momentum","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 02 Problem 08","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT20S","actor":10,"start":"2017-04-21T22:39:05.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:39:25.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 05","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT27S","actor":10,"start":"2017-04-21T22:37:21.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:37:48.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 02 Problem 19","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT32S","actor":10,"start":"2017-04-21T22:36:31.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:37:03.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Electromagnetic waves","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 14","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT100S","actor":24,"start":"2017-04-21T22:35:22.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:37:02.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Rolling motion","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 02 Problem 19","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT118S","actor":22,"start":"2017-04-21T22:34:57.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:36:55.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Circular motion","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 14","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT87S","actor":17,"start":"2017-04-21T22:35:16.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:36:43.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 5","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT151S","actor":25,"start":"2017-04-21T22:33:43.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:36:14.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Circular motion","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Spring 07 Problem 15","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT147S","actor":10,"start":"2017-04-21T22:33:28.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:35:55.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Periodic motion","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 13","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT168S","actor":17,"start":"2017-04-21T22:32:10.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:34:58.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 13","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT48S","actor":22,"start":"2017-04-21T22:33:37.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:34:25.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 12","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT73S","actor":10,"start":"2017-04-21T22:32:02.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:33:15.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Linear momentum","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 20","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT127S","actor":22,"start":"2017-04-21T22:30:50.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:32:57.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 01","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT26S","actor":26,"start":"2017-04-21T22:32:02.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:32:28.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 23","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT33S","actor":24,"start":"2017-04-21T22:31:43.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:32:16.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Current, resistance, and power","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 2 Winter 08 Problem 10","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT6S","actor":26,"start":"2017-04-21T22:31:53.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:31:59.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Periodic motion","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 06","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT48S","actor":10,"start":"2017-04-21T22:31:08.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:31:56.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 07 Problem 11","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT7S","actor":25,"start":"2017-04-21T22:31:44.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:31:51.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 13","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT20S","actor":25,"start":"2017-04-21T22:31:21.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:31:41.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 02","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT41S","actor":24,"start":"2017-04-21T22:30:42.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:31:23.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 14","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT6S","actor":25,"start":"2017-04-21T22:31:12.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:31:18.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Center of mass","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 05 Problem 06","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT116S","actor":22,"start":"2017-04-21T22:28:36.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:30:32.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Polarization","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2013 Final Exam Problem 19","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT59S","actor":24,"start":"2017-04-21T22:28:39.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:29:38.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 5","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT256S","actor":17,"start":"2017-04-21T22:24:49.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:29:05.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 07 Problem 11","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT123S","actor":25,"start":"2017-04-21T22:26:38.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:28:41.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Electromagnetic waves","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 19","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT95S","actor":24,"start":"2017-04-21T22:27:00.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:28:35.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Sound","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 17","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT24S","actor":22,"start":"2017-04-21T22:26:10.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:26:34.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 07 Problem 02","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT27S","actor":25,"start":"2017-04-21T22:25:39.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:26:06.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 07","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT179S","actor":17,"start":"2017-04-21T22:21:48.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:24:47.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Rotational kinematics","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 14","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT104S","actor":22,"start":"2017-04-21T22:22:47.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:24:31.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 02","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT3S","actor":27,"start":"2017-04-21T22:24:17.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:24:20.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 10 Problem 22","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT6S","actor":27,"start":"2017-04-21T22:23:59.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:24:05.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Mechanical waves","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 21","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT24S","actor":28,"start":"2017-04-21T22:23:25.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:23:49.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 10 Problem 22","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT15S","actor":27,"start":"2017-04-21T22:23:27.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:23:42.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 23","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT7S","actor":27,"start":"2017-04-21T22:23:18.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:23:25.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Stress and strain","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 WN2010 Problem 6","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT6S","actor":28,"start":"2017-04-21T22:23:16.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:23:22.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 13","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT7S","actor":27,"start":"2017-04-21T22:23:08.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:23:15.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Static equilibrium","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 19","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT8S","actor":28,"start":"2017-04-21T22:23:06.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:23:14.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Torque and rotational dynamics","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 16","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT8S","actor":28,"start":"2017-04-21T22:22:56.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:23:04.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Mechanical waves","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 18","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT6S","actor":28,"start":"2017-04-21T22:22:48.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:22:54.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"2D/3D kinematics","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2011 Problem 20","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT9S","actor":28,"start":"2017-04-21T22:22:37.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:22:46.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Relative motion","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2011 Problem 18","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT66S","actor":22,"start":"2017-04-21T22:21:38.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:22:44.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Projectile motion","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 24","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT14S","actor":28,"start":"2017-04-21T22:22:21.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:22:35.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 13","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT71S","actor":27,"start":"2017-04-21T22:21:09.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:22:20.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 02 Problem 04","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT13S","actor":28,"start":"2017-04-21T22:22:06.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:22:19.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Static equilibrium","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 09","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT12S","actor":28,"start":"2017-04-21T22:21:52.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:22:04.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Polarization","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2013 Final Exam Problem 19","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT48S","actor":27,"start":"2017-04-21T22:20:18.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:21:06.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Vector algebra","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Winter 04 Problem 05","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT81S","actor":22,"start":"2017-04-21T22:19:36.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:20:57.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Polarization","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 09","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT13S","actor":27,"start":"2017-04-21T22:20:01.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:20:14.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 03","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT61S","actor":25,"start":"2017-04-21T22:19:02.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:20:03.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 23","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT158S","actor":27,"start":"2017-04-21T22:16:11.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:18:49.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"AC circuits","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 3 Fall 07 Problem 12","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT37S","actor":29,"start":"2017-04-21T22:15:26.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:16:03.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Polarization","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 20","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT78S","actor":24,"start":"2017-04-21T22:14:28.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:15:46.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Mechanical energy","problem":"UM PHYSICS 481 Midterm 1 Fall 2011 Problem 03","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT47S","actor":10,"start":"2017-04-21T22:14:18.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:15:05.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 02 Problem 04","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT23S","actor":30,"start":"2017-04-21T22:14:32.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:14:55.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Mechanical waves","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam WN2010 Problem 16","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT17S","actor":10,"start":"2017-04-21T22:13:56.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:14:13.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Sound","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 08","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT23S","actor":30,"start":"2017-04-21T22:13:44.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:14:07.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Maxwell's equations","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 20","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT34S","actor":29,"start":"2017-04-21T22:13:14.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:13:48.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Moment of inertia","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 06","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT62S","actor":10,"start":"2017-04-21T22:12:18.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:13:20.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Mechanical waves","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 22","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT47S","actor":31,"start":"2017-04-21T22:12:08.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:12:55.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Periodic motion","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 20","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT106S","actor":10,"start":"2017-04-21T22:10:00.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:11:46.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Sound","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 07 Problem 04","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT354S","actor":32,"start":"2017-04-21T22:05:37.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:11:31.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 10 Problem 23","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT98S","actor":27,"start":"2017-04-21T22:08:38.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:10:16.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Relative motion","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 09 Problem 18","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT20S","actor":10,"start":"2017-04-21T22:09:35.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:09:55.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Angular momentum","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Winter 04 Problem 04","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT16S","actor":10,"start":"2017-04-21T22:09:17.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:09:33.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Rotational kinematics","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Spring 07 Problem 14","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT521S","actor":33,"start":"2017-04-21T22:00:39.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:09:20.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Stress and strain","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 18","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT51S","actor":10,"start":"2017-04-21T22:08:19.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:09:10.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 09","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT12S","actor":34,"start":"2017-04-21T22:08:47.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:08:59.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Polarization","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 09","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT38S","actor":27,"start":"2017-04-21T22:07:50.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:08:28.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 09","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT51S","actor":25,"start":"2017-04-21T22:07:24.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:08:15.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Polarization","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 04","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT72S","actor":27,"start":"2017-04-21T22:06:36.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:07:48.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 WN2010 Problem 18","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT223S","actor":10,"start":"2017-04-21T22:03:56.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:07:39.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 14","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT13S","actor":25,"start":"2017-04-21T22:06:31.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:06:44.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 14","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT135S","actor":34,"start":"2017-04-21T22:04:28.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:06:43.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Relative motion","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 17","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT305S","actor":35,"start":"2017-04-21T22:01:34.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:06:39.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 14","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT122S","actor":25,"start":"2017-04-21T22:04:11.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:06:13.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Polarization","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 20","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT1558S","actor":27,"start":"2017-04-21T21:40:00.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:05:58.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Rotational kinematics","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 11","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT442S","actor":32,"start":"2017-04-21T21:58:13.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:05:35.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Collisions","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 08","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT102S","actor":35,"start":"2017-04-21T21:59:29.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:01:11.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Static equilibrium","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 02 Problem 16","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT93S","actor":36,"start":"2017-04-21T21:59:35.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:01:08.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Mechanical waves","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 6","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT276S","actor":37,"start":"2017-04-21T21:55:59.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T22:00:35.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 WN2010 Problem 17","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT95S","actor":31,"start":"2017-04-21T21:58:15.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:59:50.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Work and kinetic energy","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 FA2010 Problem 10","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT321S","actor":33,"start":"2017-04-21T21:54:16.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:59:37.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Stress and strain","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 18","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT254S","actor":35,"start":"2017-04-21T21:55:10.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:59:24.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Mechanical waves","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 02 Problem 13","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT215S","actor":38,"start":"2017-04-21T21:54:38.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:58:13.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 05","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT985S","actor":31,"start":"2017-04-21T21:41:48.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:58:13.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Shell theorem / spherical mass distributions","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 WN2010 Problem 20","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT38S","actor":10,"start":"2017-04-21T21:57:12.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:57:50.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Static equilibrium","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 07 Problem 13","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT110S","actor":36,"start":"2017-04-21T21:55:45.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:57:35.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 11","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT224S","actor":32,"start":"2017-04-21T21:53:16.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:57:00.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Mechanical energy","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 05 Problem 17","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT38S","actor":10,"start":"2017-04-21T21:56:09.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:56:47.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Moment of inertia","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 14","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT6S","actor":10,"start":"2017-04-21T21:56:01.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:56:07.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 19","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT1140S","actor":37,"start":"2017-04-21T21:36:54.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:55:54.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Torque and rotational dynamics","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 07 Problem 06","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT29S","actor":39,"start":"2017-04-21T21:55:24.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:55:53.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Forces","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 03","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT202S","actor":39,"start":"2017-04-21T21:51:57.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:55:19.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 13","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT335S","actor":36,"start":"2017-04-21T21:49:34.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:55:09.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Forces","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 05 Problem 10","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT129S","actor":38,"start":"2017-04-21T21:52:11.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:54:20.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Mechanical waves","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 23","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT30S","actor":10,"start":"2017-04-21T21:52:55.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:53:25.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Shell theorem / spherical mass distributions","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 02 Problem 11","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT464S","actor":32,"start":"2017-04-21T21:45:24.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:53:08.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Polarization","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2013 Final Exam Problem 19","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT54S","actor":15,"start":"2017-04-21T21:52:13.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:53:07.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 23","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT789S","actor":40,"start":"2017-04-21T21:39:40.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:52:49.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Collisions","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 05 Problem 09","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT458S","actor":33,"start":"2017-04-21T21:44:49.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:52:27.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Gravitational force / potential energy","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 07 Problem 19","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT125S","actor":10,"start":"2017-04-21T21:50:14.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:52:19.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 02","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT152S","actor":15,"start":"2017-04-21T21:49:34.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:52:06.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Mechanical waves","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 07","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT28S","actor":38,"start":"2017-04-21T21:51:37.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:52:05.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 08","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT143S","actor":39,"start":"2017-04-21T21:49:30.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:51:53.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 05","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT30S","actor":41,"start":"2017-04-21T21:50:23.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:50:53.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Mechanical waves","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Final Exam Problem 20","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT26S","actor":41,"start":"2017-04-21T21:49:44.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:50:10.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 07 Problem 09","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT208S","actor":42,"start":"2017-04-21T21:46:13.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:49:41.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Gravitational force / potential energy","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 8","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT361S","actor":35,"start":"2017-04-21T21:43:38.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:49:39.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Polarization","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 09","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT26S","actor":15,"start":"2017-04-21T21:48:53.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:49:19.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Mechanical waves","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 07 Problem 21","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT74S","actor":39,"start":"2017-04-21T21:48:05.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:49:19.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Circular motion","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Spring 07 Problem 14","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT106S","actor":36,"start":"2017-04-21T21:47:29.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:49:15.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Periodic motion","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 07 Problem 21","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT1876S","actor":10,"start":"2017-04-21T21:17:58.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:49:14.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"RC circuits","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 08","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT10S","actor":26,"start":"2017-04-21T21:48:51.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:49:01.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 23","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT140S","actor":15,"start":"2017-04-21T21:46:31.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:48:51.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Current, resistance, and power","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 2 Winter 08 Problem 07","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT15S","actor":26,"start":"2017-04-21T21:48:34.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:48:49.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Flux and Gauss' law","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 20","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT145S","actor":26,"start":"2017-04-21T21:46:06.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:48:31.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Mechanical waves","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 20","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT10S","actor":39,"start":"2017-04-21T21:47:47.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:47:57.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Stress and strain","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 WN2010 Problem 6","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT508S","actor":39,"start":"2017-04-21T21:39:08.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:47:36.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Moment of inertia","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 9","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT222S","actor":36,"start":"2017-04-21T21:43:46.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:47:28.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"1D kinematics","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 14","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT364S","actor":38,"start":"2017-04-21T21:40:59.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:47:03.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Mechanical waves","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 09","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT32S","actor":43,"start":"2017-04-21T21:46:20.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:46:52.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Electromagnetic waves","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 15","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT20S","actor":26,"start":"2017-04-21T21:45:43.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:46:03.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Mechanical waves","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 07 Problem 06","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT72S","actor":43,"start":"2017-04-21T21:44:48.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:46:00.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Mechanical energy","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 09 Problem 13","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT36S","actor":32,"start":"2017-04-21T21:44:47.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:45:23.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Periodic motion","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 04","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT233S","actor":32,"start":"2017-04-21T21:40:53.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:44:46.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 13","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT34S","actor":43,"start":"2017-04-21T21:43:59.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:44:33.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Orbits / Kepler's laws","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 FA2010 Problem 3","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT16S","actor":20,"start":"2017-04-21T21:43:59.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:44:15.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Moment of inertia","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Fall 02 Problem 19","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT86S","actor":33,"start":"2017-04-21T21:42:42.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:44:08.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Periodic motion","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 03","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT186S","actor":20,"start":"2017-04-21T21:40:51.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:43:57.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Linear momentum","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 WN2010 Problem 11","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT420S","actor":44,"start":"2017-04-21T21:36:49.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:43:49.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Relative motion","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Winter 04 Problem 02","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT126S","actor":36,"start":"2017-04-21T21:41:35.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:43:41.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Conservative forces and potential energy","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 05 Problem 08","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT264S","actor":35,"start":"2017-04-21T21:39:13.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:43:37.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 10 Problem 23","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT83S","actor":26,"start":"2017-04-21T21:41:49.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:43:12.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 01","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT96S","actor":43,"start":"2017-04-21T21:41:31.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:43:07.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 21","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT93S","actor":45,"start":"2017-04-21T21:40:54.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:42:27.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Newton's laws","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2011 Problem 14","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT266S","actor":33,"start":"2017-04-21T21:37:20.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:41:46.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Electric fields","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 11","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT289S","actor":26,"start":"2017-04-21T21:36:57.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:41:46.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Work and kinetic energy","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam FA2010 Problem 5","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT70S","actor":38,"start":"2017-04-21T21:39:47.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:40:57.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 FA2010 Problem 16","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT228S","actor":31,"start":"2017-04-21T21:37:04.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:40:52.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Newton's laws","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 07 Problem 01","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT260S","actor":32,"start":"2017-04-21T21:36:32.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:40:52.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 21","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT48S","actor":45,"start":"2017-04-21T21:40:03.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:40:51.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 05","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT64S","actor":20,"start":"2017-04-21T21:39:46.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:40:50.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Electric potential energy","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Winter 10 Problem 08","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT110S","actor":46,"start":"2017-04-21T21:38:44.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:40:34.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Polarization","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Final Exam Problem 04","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT22S","actor":45,"start":"2017-04-21T21:39:40.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:40:02.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Fall 10 Problem 21","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT43S","actor":27,"start":"2017-04-21T21:39:15.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:39:58.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Mechanical waves","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 06","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT51S","actor":38,"start":"2017-04-21T21:38:55.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:39:46.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Rolling motion","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 Winter 04 Problem 20","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT26S","actor":20,"start":"2017-04-21T21:39:19.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:39:45.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2013 Final Exam Problem 21","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT884S","actor":45,"start":"2017-04-21T21:24:52.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:39:36.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Center of mass","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 05","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT40S","actor":20,"start":"2017-04-21T21:38:22.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:39:02.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Vector algebra","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 WN2010 Problem 19","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT28S","actor":35,"start":"2017-04-21T21:38:32.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:39:00.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Vector algebra","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 19","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT65S","actor":38,"start":"2017-04-21T21:37:49.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:38:54.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Electric dipoles","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 20","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT124S","actor":46,"start":"2017-04-21T21:36:37.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:38:41.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Rotational kinematics","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 11","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT400S","actor":38,"start":"2017-04-21T21:31:07.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:37:47.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Work and kinetic energy","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 01","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT75S","actor":39,"start":"2017-04-21T21:36:15.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:37:30.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Shell theorem / spherical mass distributions","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 21","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT153S","actor":20,"start":"2017-04-21T21:34:33.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:37:06.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 07","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT67S","actor":31,"start":"2017-04-21T21:35:54.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:37:01.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Final Exam Problem 02","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT173S","actor":27,"start":"2017-04-21T21:34:07.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:37:00.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Rolling motion","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 09 Problem 19","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT45S","actor":44,"start":"2017-04-21T21:35:52.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:36:37.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Polarization","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 24","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT126S","actor":46,"start":"2017-04-21T21:34:26.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:36:32.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Circular motion","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Fall 02 Problem 19","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT336S","actor":32,"start":"2017-04-21T21:30:55.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:36:31.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Mechanical waves","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 21","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT72S","actor":37,"start":"2017-04-21T21:34:54.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:36:06.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Periodic motion","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 FA2010 Problem 11","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT7S","actor":44,"start":"2017-04-21T21:35:44.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:35:51.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 02 Problem 09","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT2011S","actor":31,"start":"2017-04-21T21:02:18.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:35:49.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Capacitance","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 3 Winter 06 Problem 19","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT16S","actor":26,"start":"2017-04-21T21:35:28.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:35:44.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Polarization","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Final Exam Problem 23","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT26S","actor":26,"start":"2017-04-21T21:34:58.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:35:24.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Electric dipoles","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 09","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT21S","actor":26,"start":"2017-04-21T21:34:30.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:34:51.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Mechanical waves","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam WN2010 Problem 16","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT6S","actor":37,"start":"2017-04-21T21:34:36.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:34:42.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Stress and strain","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 20","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT338S","actor":20,"start":"2017-04-21T21:28:50.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:34:28.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Transformers","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 3 Fall 07 Problem 07","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT69S","actor":26,"start":"2017-04-21T21:33:17.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:34:26.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Linear momentum","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 FA2010 Problem 6","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT92S","actor":44,"start":"2017-04-21T21:32:51.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:34:23.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Electric potential","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 1 Fall 10 Problem 16","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT178S","actor":46,"start":"2017-04-21T21:31:22.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:34:20.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Sound","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 12","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT102S","actor":37,"start":"2017-04-21T21:32:31.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:34:13.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 01","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT41S","actor":27,"start":"2017-04-21T21:33:22.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:34:03.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Center of mass","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Spring 07 Problem 07","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT139S","actor":47,"start":"2017-04-21T21:31:17.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:33:36.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Polarization","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2013 Final Exam Problem 23","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT23S","actor":27,"start":"2017-04-21T21:32:56.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:33:19.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Polarization","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2013 Final Exam Problem 19","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT15S","actor":26,"start":"2017-04-21T21:32:51.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:33:06.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Polarization","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 11 Problem 24","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT74S","actor":27,"start":"2017-04-21T21:31:39.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:32:53.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Mechanical energy","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Midterm Exam 2 Problem 10","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT162S","actor":44,"start":"2017-04-21T21:30:07.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:32:49.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 7","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT62S","actor":41,"start":"2017-04-21T21:31:34.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:32:36.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Polarization","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 14","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT128S","actor":27,"start":"2017-04-21T21:29:27.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:31:35.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Collisions","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Fall 09 Problem 11","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT80S","actor":38,"start":"2017-04-21T21:29:45.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:31:05.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Ampere's law","problem":"UM Physics 240 Midterm 3 Winter 06 Problem 05","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT83S","actor":46,"start":"2017-04-21T21:29:40.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:31:03.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Relative motion","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 1 Spring 07 Problem 08","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT247S","actor":32,"start":"2017-04-21T21:26:47.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:30:54.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Sound","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 05 Problem 17","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT99S","actor":41,"start":"2017-04-21T21:28:21.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:30:00.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Mechanical waves","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Final Exam Problem 9","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT181S","actor":38,"start":"2017-04-21T21:26:43.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:29:44.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Transformers","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 10 Problem 12","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT132S","actor":46,"start":"2017-04-21T21:27:24.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:29:36.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Shell theorem / spherical mass distributions","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 3 FA2010 Problem 9","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT182S","actor":44,"start":"2017-04-21T21:26:24.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:29:26.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Polarization","problem":"UM Physics 240 Final Exam Spring 10 Problem 21","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT48S","actor":27,"start":"2017-04-21T21:28:36.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:29:24.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Fluid dynamics","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Winter 04 Problem 05","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT128S","actor":41,"start":"2017-04-21T21:26:05.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:28:13.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Sound","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Fall 2011 Final Exam Problem 14","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT302S","actor":20,"start":"2017-04-21T21:23:03.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:28:05.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Refraction and reflection","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2013 Final Exam Problem 21","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT82S","actor":27,"start":"2017-04-21T21:26:43.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:28:05.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Electric potential","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Winter 2012 Midterm Exam 1 Problem 11","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT67S","actor":46,"start":"2017-04-21T21:26:03.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:27:10.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Mechanical waves","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Final Exam Problem 9","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT184S","actor":32,"start":"2017-04-21T21:23:32.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:26:36.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Center of mass","problem":"UM Physics 140 Midterm 2 Spring 07 Problem 04","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT355S","actor":47,"start":"2017-04-21T21:20:09.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:26:04.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Fluid statics / bouyancy","problem":"UM Physics 140 Final Exam Fall 02 Problem 19","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT22S","actor":41,"start":"2017-04-21T21:25:39.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:26:01.000Z","class":"Physics 140"},{"problem_set":"Ampere's law","problem":"UM PHYSICS 240 Fall 2013 Final Exam Problem 12","answerCorrect":"true","time":"PT57S","actor":46,"start":"2017-04-21T21:25:03.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:26:00.000Z","class":"Physics 240"},{"problem_set":"Sound","problem":"UM PHYSICS 140 Winter 2011 Midterm Exam 3 Problem 12","answerCorrect":"false","time":"PT8S","actor":44,"start":"2017-04-21T21:25:40.000Z","end":"2017-04-21T21:25:48.000Z","class":"Physics 140"}]
